oncontracting.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy | OnContracting

**PRIVACY POLICY**

OnContracting is committed and serious about protecting your privacy.  Please read and learn more about our privacy policy. 

By visiting the OnContracting website (the “Website”), submitting information or using any of our services (the “OnContracting Service”), or creating an account to use the OnContracting Services (a “OnContracting Account”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What is Covered in This Privacy Policy?**

This Privacy Policy covers OnContracting's treatment of personally identifiable information (collectively with “Submitted Information” (as defined herein), the "Personal Information") that OnContracting gathers when you are accessing the Website and when you use the OnContracting Service or register for a OnContracting Account.  Furthermore, this Privacy Policy covers OnContracting's treatment of any Personal Information that OnContracting's business partners share with OnContracting.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that OnContracting does not own or control, or to individuals that OnContracting does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information is Collected by OnContracting?**

The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, website URL, e-mail address, blog or other personal website URL, your nickname or screenname, and any other information that would allow OnContracting to identify you or contact you if needed. 

In addition to the Personal Information mentioned, we may ask you to provide certain other information such as general demographic information, including age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, and interests.  The information we gather from our users enables us to personalize and improve the OnContracting Service.   

We may receive and store any information you enter on the Website or provide to us in any other way.  The Personal Information you provide may be used for providing attribution to comments you post, to operate and improve the Website, and to better deliver the OnContracting Service.  

If you do not want us to collect your personal information, please do not provide it to us.

**Information from Social Networking Websites**

By registering for a OnContracting Account, you may have the option to sign in using third party social networking websites (collectively, the “Social Networks”), such as Facebook, Google or LinkedIn.  If you choose to sign in through these Social Networks or services, we use the information you have already provided to such Social Networks in registering for an account with such Social Networks and which you have allowed such Social Networks to share with OnContracting, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, email, your user profile picture, your friends and contacts list, pages, your gender, and the networks to which you belong (collectively, your “Submitted Information”). 

You expressly authorize us to collect and use your Submitted Information in connection with your use of the OnContracting Services  You further acknowledge and agree that OnContracting may, but is not obligated to, maintain copies of your Submitted Information indefinitely, or delete any or all Submitted Information, at our sole discretion.

We advise you to carefully read to the terms of use and privacy policies of these Social Networks. It is your responsibility to read and accept the respective Policies prior to signing into your OnContracting Account through such Social Networks.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website and/or OnContracting Service.  OnContracting may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 

OnContracting uses "cookies" to collect non-personal data and information.  Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, and is typically placed on your hard disk by a web page server.  Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.   The way cookies function is by assigning a number to the user that has no meaning outside of the assigning website.

You should be aware that OnContracting cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by OnContracting's third-party partners or advertisers.  You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of the Website and OnContracting Service that depend on cookies.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will be used only by OnContracting and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent.  

OnContracting occasionally hires other companies to provide limited administrative and communication services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, or performing statistical analysis of the Services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only such personal information as necessary for them to deliver the service. Those companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.  You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. 

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets.  In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred.  Moreover, if OnContracting, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.  You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of OnContracting may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

OnContracting may access and/or disclose personal information about you or your account without your prior consent if OnContracting has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of OnContracting (including the enforcement of our agreements); (iii) enforce the Terms of Use, which can be accessed at  <http://www.oncontracting.com/pg/useragreement.html> (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of the Services or equipment as authorized by law; or (vi) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of OnContracting Services or members of the public.

OnContracting may also share your personal information for the following reasons

  * To allow job seekers to post resumes;
  * To allow recruiters to post job openings and search resumes. These jobs will be listed and indexed in our Web Site as well as search engines, which may be searchable either directly or indirectly by job seekers, other registered users, and corporations;
  * To allow other recruiters to contact you online via the Web Site or through email or phone if you have provided these as options;
  * To enable you to contact us and provide feedback, and to enable us to respond to your comments and requests for assistance;
  * To improve our marketing and advertising efforts;
  * To provide you with our own and third-party product and content offerings that may interest you including newsletters, surveys and career advice;
  * To enable you to use the “Forward this to a Friend” and “Referral” features;
  * To enable unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents, or independent contractors to help us maintain our Web Site and to provide any other administrative service to us (including, but not limited to, hosting our web servers, providing market research analysis, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance);
  * To affiliates, strategic partners, agents, third party marketers or other unaffiliated parties who are offering products or services that we believe may be of interest to you or who require your personally identifiable information for research, administrative and/or internal business purposes. These parties may use your personally identifiable information to contact you with an offer or advertisement related to a product or service, or they may use such information for their own research, administration or business purposes. If you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information in this manner, please do not provide us with this information;
  * To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets;
  * To send account statements and invoices to users;
  * To enforce or apply any of the terms of our user agreements;
  * To protect and defend our rights and property, and to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our users;
  * To contact you about Web Site updates, informational and service-related communications, including important security updates;
  * To generate internal reports about the use of our Web Site;
  * To publish the jobs in third party job feed sites;
  * To post jobs and upload resumes received through E-Mails, XML Feeds, and APIs.

Even if your resume or corporate profile from our web site is removed, there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, logs, and other records. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes. However, OnContracting reserves the right, to re-contact former users of our web site.

**Security and Protection of Personal Information**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and store Personal Information collected in a database.  However, while we employ reasonable standards of security, no security system is impenetrable.   For most internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions you submit or create accounts that give them access to this information.  As such, OnContracting cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to OnContracting over the internet.  We recommend that you do not disclose your password or confirmation number (as applicable) to anyone. We also recommend you do not share information that is not necessary for example your personal address, phone number, other details as most communication can be done via messages in the system and/or by email.

**E-mail Communications**

Upon registration for events and/or services provided by OnContracting, we may send you daily or weekly e-mails.  If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please change your settings in the website. However, after you unsubscribe to cease receiving e-mails, OnContracting may still contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including messages regarding the administration of your account and/or any services or events to which you have registered.

**Advertisements Displayed by Third Parties**

OnContracting may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Website.  Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display.  These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers’ websites.  OnContracting has no access to or control over cookies of these links to other websites and organizations, nor does OnContracting have control over or access to cookies by OnContracting’s third-party partners or advertisers.  This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third-party advertiser or ad server may collect from you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy  **

OnContracting retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, in its sole discretion.  Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.  If we make changes in the way we use your Personal Information such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting.  You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.  Your continued access or use of the Website and/or the OnContracting Service shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

**Questions or Comments Regarding this Privacy Policy**

OnContracting welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use, or share your Personal Information.  Any such questions or comments should be submitted via [email](mailto:info@oncontracting.com?subject=Re%3A%20Privacy%20Policy) or by contacting us. We will make every effort to resolve or answer your concern. You can read more [about OnContracting here](http://www.oncontracting.com/pg/aboutus.html).

**Modifications of this Privacy Notice**

ONCONTRACTING MAY MODIFY THIS PRIVACY NOTICE AT ANY TIME, IN ONCONTRACTING’S SOLE DISCRETION, AND SUCH MODIFICATION SHALL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON EITHER POSTING OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE ON THE WEBSITE OR NOTIFYING YOU. YOU AGREE TO REVIEW THIS PRIVACY NOTICE PERIODICALLY TO ENSURE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY MODIFICATIONS. YOUR CONTINUED ACCESS OR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE SOFTWARE SHALL BE DEEMED YOUR CONCLUSIVE ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE.
